

Profile

I am a Junior Software Developer who travels a consistent path for self-growth, knowledge, and problem solving. My experience includes technical and creative projects, developing the skill to see things from a broad perspective. My work ethic, creative/technical mind, and communication skills are the foundations to my current, as well as future success.

Experience

Bar Manager, Market Tavern, Sykesville, MD

JULY 2017 — AUGUST 2020

- Provided bar patrons with optimal customer service.
- Acted as a support to other bartenders by creating drinks, and helping to maintain and stock the bar when necessary.
- Monitored bar inventory and made notes for needed supplies when necessary.
- Managed beginning/end of day operations.

Fellow at Software Engineering Immersive, General Assembly

SEPTEMBER 2020 — DECEMBER 2020

- Developed full stack projects with both frontend and backend frameworks.
- Developed in team environments, as well as collaborative environments with UX teams.

Education

Digital Media and Web Technologies, University of Maryland - University College,

 ${\tt AUGUST~2018-MAY~2019}$

General Studies, Carroll Community College

AUGUST 2012 — DECEMBER 2014

References

Jennifer Truby from Market Tavern

jen@market-tavern.com · 410-991-0216

Projects

BookShelf

Store Manager

Ballot Request App

Details

7556 Main Street, Sykesville, MD, 21784, United States

briand.nester@gmail.com

github.com/cyberdragonwizard

linkedin.com/in/brian-nester-6a168710b

443-340-7456

Languages

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

Ruby

Other

React

Mongoose

Express

Rails

MongoDB

Postgres

Material UI